zoig.com 2019-05-08

# ZOIG.COM - Privacy policy

### A Special Note About Children

Children under eighteen years of age are not eligible to use our services. We ask that children not submit information to us.

### About ZOIG.COM and Information We Collect

ZOIG.COM is an online community which provides an easy way to post your amateur photos and videos and view media files submitted by other members. ZOIG.COM is FREE to all qualified members.

In our online anonymous registration form, we ask you to provide us with certain information such as your age, you location, date of birth, gender, sexual preference.

In the course of using our site, we automatically track certain information such as your IP addresses and email addresses. Many sites automatically collect this information.

### Our Use of Your Information

We internally use personally identifiable information of our users to improve our marketing efforts, to statistically analyze site usage, to improve our content and product offerings as well as to customize our site's content and layout. We believe these uses allow us to improve our site and better tailor your online experience to meet your needs.

We may also use personally identifiable information about you to deliver information to you that, in some cases, are targeted to your interests, such as targeted banners and promotions.

We also send periodic informational updates to our members via email and/or private message on the site and as a member of ZOIG.COM you agree to receive them.

We use personally identifiable information to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our User Agreement.

### Our Disclosure of Your Information

We do not and will never sell or rent any personally identifiable information about you to any third party without your permission. We do disclose information in aggregate to advertisers and for other marketing and promotional purposes. However, in these situations, we DO NOT disclose to these entities any information that could be used to personally identify you. Certain information, such as your password, is not disclosed in aggregate at all.

In order to maintain a healthy community, ZOIG.COM cooperates with all law enforcement inquiries and with all third parties to enforce their intellectual property or other rights.

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site. We use a credit card processing companies to bill you for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes. 

### Your use of Other Users' Information

You may not use other user's information for commercial purposes, to spam, to harass, or to make unlawful threats. ZOIG.COM reserves the right to terminate those who misuse other user's information or who otherwise abuse ZOIG.COM.

### Control of Your Password

You may not disclose your password to any third parties or share it with any third parties. If, despite the foregoing, you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personally identifiable information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password.

### Third Party Collections of Information

Our policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. To the extent that you disclose your information to other parties on our system or other sites throughout the Internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the personal information you disclose to them. While ZOIG.COM is working closely with our partners to ensure the highest privacy to you, we encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others.

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gifs or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness.

### Security

ZOIG.COM has security measures in place to protect and prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. ZOIG.COM uses industry standard efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal identifiable information such as firewalls. While "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet, our technical experts at ZOIG.COM work hard to ensure your secure use of our services.

### Update/Delete

ZOIG.COM Members have the following choices to modify or delete their information from our database:

* [Contact us](https://www.zoig.com/contact);

* [Log in](https://www.zoig.com/login) with your password and modify/delete your profile;

Effective on: (Jan 10, 2007)
